[{"answer": "Kid Rock is the quintessential all-American rock star.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 2, "question": "Who the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) is Piers Morgan?", "qSentId": 1}, {"answer": "It doesn't really matter to me.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Are you Mr. Rock?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "And if I had 100 bucks every time somebody asked that.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "I mean is there a point where you'd have to change your name from Kid?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "I enjoy to have a good time.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "You like being a rocker?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Probably wilder than I'm willing to discuss right now.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How wild does it get?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Do you know how much you've consumed over the years?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I like who I am.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "It's what rock stars do, isn't it?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Is there anything you regret?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "You'd say nothing?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Great.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "How do you feel about being 40?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Because I can't fight it.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think I'll be able to rock for a while.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "At what point does it become embarrassing?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "\"Vanity Fair\" magazine.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "What's it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "There's always a Justin Bieber.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "He just kind of chuckled then.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Yes, sure there is.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Do you think there's room for everyone in music?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "It's honest.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, I'm sure I've been dishonest at times.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Have you ever been dishonest?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Wherever you want to start.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Jeez, where do you want to start?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "With flying colors.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I mean I'd say that's been the stupid stuff, you know, the fights in Waffle Houses and the, you know, different things like that.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Are you -- are you only ever violent when you've been drinking?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Would you -- could I actually be in fear of a right hook?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "So you can control it when you're in this environment?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "When do you feel it descending?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "But you don't regret smacking Tommy Lee, do you?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "He deserved it?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Waffle House guy, does he deserve what came his way?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Seventeen.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "How old is he now?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, I never really paddled him that much.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "How have you been different as a father, do you think?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "No, he got a -- he got a few.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "I mean you've never smacked your son?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Nothing -- nothing like you got?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "ID ROCK: Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I think I've been a good dad.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "But what kind of dad do you think you've been?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Show respect to the people around you, especially have a little respect for as much as I'm gone -- and I've tried to adjust my schedule to be home.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "What do you think the law of the land should be for your son?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he actually attended Malibu High School for like one month.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "If he started taking drugs or stuff, would you be censorious about that?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "It's where I'm from.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "What does it mean to you?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "When you sing about Detroit, what's going through your mind?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "As often as I can.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "How often do you do that?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, when it really started hitting -- you know, Detroit has been devastated for a lot of years and it's been going that way.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "And where is it now?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "You couldn't do a LeBron and -- and switch allegiance to another city?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "You can't be bought, can you?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "It kind of does, yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "And money brings you that power, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "No, it's a weird thing.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Or do you feel you put enough back into that city?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I think a -- an original 1930 Cadillac.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What's the most extravagant thing you've ever bought?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "It was just under a half a million dollars.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "How much was that?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Are you a traditional Republican?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I think I'm -- I'm -- I think I'm like the majority of people who are tired of the -- wouldn't want a bunch of bible thumpers running the country and we don't want a bunch of pot smoking hippies running it.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "You're more for your country than you are for a party?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "You know, that's tough to say, because, you know, it's -- when you get into politics, I know -- I know this much, I don't study political science and I didn't do that well in school.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Do you -- do you think the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq have been just wars?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Well, we -- we need to have a presence there.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "I mean are we -- are we winning these wars, from what you've seen on the ground?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "When you're on a plane with human remains and there's an American flag draped over a casket you're flying with, you know, it really sparks up some things and really makes you think.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "And it's difficult, I think, if you look at it, you know, are we winning, do you think, from what you've seen there?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Misunderstood.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Still, when you do, what do you think the perception of your country is?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I think the freedom to do whatever you want, you know, with -- without taking advantage.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "And what -- what does being an American mean to you?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I don't know, sometimes I shake a finger at those Baby Boomers.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "And do you feel that the American dream is still what it used to be?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I've -- I have actually interviewed --", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "What, do you live in a cave?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I'm not going to get into it.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Because she's a crazy, crazy chick, right?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Well, who are you going to argue about that with?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "I'm not taking the bait.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I've learned lessons all through life.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "You learned lessons, didn't you?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Is there anyone special in your life?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Do you care to elaborate?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that's always been in my makeup.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Do you think that's in your makeup?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Chris Rock said that years ago in his comedy vignettes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "-- I mean it's just outrageous, isn't it?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Just totally.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "No, I mean you got lucky?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Has it -- has it been all you hoped it would be?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "And do you like being famous?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "How much have you made?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "None of your business.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Do you know how much you make?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I -- I guess you could say that.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "How rich you are?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I think so, yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Is it the best you've done, do you think?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Are you an emotional guy?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "When I found out my dad had a heart attack.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "When was the last time you cried?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Whether you care about somebody, you care about your family deeply.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "What -- what does that tell you when that sort of thing happens to you in life?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Jeez, I don't know.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "If you knew you were going to die tomorrow, what would be the one thing you'd like to relive?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "It depends to who.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "How important to you is your credibility?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Well, it's very deep and it's very honest and I'm going to be very candid with you.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "What's the principal at stake here for you?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Is that your lighter?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "The Handsome Pad in Kensington.", "docId": "110310pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "What's your pub called?", "qSentId": 791}]